Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 28-131)
  - Show Music (Box 28-91, 107-126)
    - Carousel, 1945, Music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Script; 1945 Jan. 9 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Catch a star!, 1955, Various writers
      - Everybody wants to be in show business, Lead sheet; No lyric (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Choose your partner see Courtin' time
    - Christmas in Las Vegas, circa 1965, Title song by Walker and Arnold Goland
      - Christmas in Las Vegas, Piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 32/16)
      - Opening Act I, Full score (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Comic strip, 1958, Play by George Panetta, title song by Don Walker and William C. Whitman
      - Comic strip, Piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 32/18)
      - Sad strip/Strip vocal/Wild strip/Untitled, Scores (Box-folder 32/19)
      - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 32/20)
      - Cover mock ups (Box-folder 32/21)
    - A Connecticut yankee, 1943 revival, Music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Camelot samba, Piano-vocal scores and lyric sheet (Box-folder 32/22)
      - Full scores
        - I feel at home with you overture/Bows (Box-folder 32/23)
        - Overture B (Box-folder 32/24)
        - Intro to overture (Box-folder 32/25)
        - You always love the same girl (Box-folder 32/26)
    - The cool mikado see The mikado
    - Courtin' time, 1951, Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Jack Lawrence
      - Full scores
        - Araminta's soliloquy (Box-folder 110/1)
        - Bee scene closing (new) (Box-folder 110/2)
        - Change to bee scene (Box-folder 110/3)
        - Choose your partner (Box-folder 110/4)
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 110/5)
        - Entr'acte-Fixin' (Box-folder 110/6)
        - Farmer's exit (Box-folder 110/7)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 110/8)
        - Fixin' for a long cold winter reprise (Box-folder 110/9)
        - Good-bye! dear friend! good-bye! (Box-folder 110/10)
        - Hangover blues (Box-folder 110/11)
        - Hat in hand (Box-folder 110/12)
        - I do! He doesn't! (Box-folder 110/13)
        - Johnny-ride-the-sky (Box-folder 110/14)
        - Johnny-ride-the-sky reprise (Box-folder 110/15)
        - Maine will remember the Maine (Box-folder 110/16)
        - Masculinity (Box-folder 110/17)
        - My golden moment (Box-folder 110/18)
        - An old fashioned glimmer in your eye (Box-folder 110/19)
        - An old fashioned glimmer in your eye encore (Box-folder 110/20)
        - Opening Act I (Box-folder 110/21)
        - Overture (Box-folder 111/1)
        - Post office opening (Box-folder 111/2)
        - Proposal cue (Box-folder 111/3)
        - Saddle the chestnut! (Box-folder 111/4)
        - The sensible thing to do (Box-folder 111/5)
        - Smile a while (Box-folder 111/6)
        - Strong man act (Box-folder 111/7)
        - Today at your house, tomorrow at mine (Box-folder 111/8)
        - Too much trouble (Box-folder 111/9)
        - Weathervane concerto (Box-folder 111/10)
        - Wishbone reprise (Box-folder 111/11)
        - Wishbone waltz (Box-folder 111/12)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified (Box-folder 111/1)
      - Piano-vocal scores/piano scores/short scores/vocal arrangements
        - The answer is "ee-yes!" (Box-folder 33/1)
        - The answer is "ee-yes!" reprise (Box-folder 33/2)
        - Araminta's soliloquy (Box-folder 33/3)
        - Araminta's transition (Box-folder 33/4)
        - Bee scene closing (Box-folder 33/5)
        - Change to bee scene (Box-folder 33/6)
        - Choose your partner (Box-folder 33/7)
        - Crackerbarrel bunk (Box-folder 33/8)
        - Exit #14 (Box-folder 33/9)
        - Farmer's exit (Box-folder 33/10)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 33/11)
        - Finale Act II (Box-folder 33/12)
        - Fixin' for a long, cold winter (Box-folder 33/13)
        - Fixin' for a long, cold winter #2a (Box-folder 33/14)
        - Good-bye, dear friend, good-bye (Box-folder 34/1)
        - Hangover blues (Box-folder 34/2)
        - Harriet's song (If I could fit inside an envelope) (Box-folder 34/3)
        - Hat in hand (Box-folder 34/4)
        - Heart in hand (Box-folder 34/5)
        - How long the night (Box-folder 34/6)
        - I do-he doesn't (Box-folder 34/7)
        - If I could fit inside an envelope (I'd mail myself away) see Harriet's song and Pencil origins
        - Johnny ride the sky (Box-folder 34/8)
        - Johnny ride the sky last chorus (Box-folder 34/9)
        - Johnny ride the sky reprise (Box-folder 34/10)
        - Kiss #2 (#1c) (Box-folder 34/11)
        - Maine will remember the Maine (Box-folder 34/12)
        - Making love on paper (Box-folder 34/13)
        - A man never marries a wife (Box-folder 35/1-2)
        - A man never marries a wife tag (Box-folder 35/3)
        - Masculinity! (Box-folder 35/4)
        - Masculinity encore (Box-folder 35/5)
        - Morning after, Full score sketch (Box-folder 35/6)
        - My golden moment (Box-folder 35/7)
        - My golden moment-chorus II (Box-folder 35/8)
        - Not I! (Box-folder 35/9)
        - An old fashioned glimmer in your eye (Box-folder 35/10-11)
        - Opening Act I (Box-folder 35/12)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 35/13)
        - Overture see Discarded full scores
        - Post office opening (Box-folder 35/14)
        - Saddle the chestnut! (Box-folder 35/15)
        - Sam's fury (Box-folder 35/16)
        - The sensible thing to do (Box-folder 35/17-36/1)
        - Settin' my cap for you (Box-folder 36/2)
        - Smile a while (Box-folder 36/3)
        - Smile a while reprise (Box-folder 36/4)
        - Strong man act (Box-folder 36/5)
        - Today at your house, tomorrow at mine (Box-folder 36/6-7)
        - Too much trouble (Box-folder 36/8)
        - Up our broad Penobscot (Box-folder 36/9)
        - Weathervane concertino (Box-folder 36/10)
        - Weathervane concerto (Box-folder 36/11)
        - Weathervane rhapsody (Box-folder 37/1)
        - The wishbone song (Box-folder 37/2)
        - The wishbone song reprise (Box-folder 37/3)
        - Wishbone waltz (Box-folder 37/4)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified music (Box-folder 37/5)
      - Parts
        - Reed 1 (flute) (Box-folder 37/6)
        - Reed 2 (Box-folder 37/7-8)
        - Reed 3 (oboe) (Box-folder 38/1)
        - Reed 4 (bass clarinet) (Box-folder 38/2)
        - Bassoon (Box-folder 38/3)
        - Horns (Box-folder 38/4-5)
        - Trumpets (Box-folder 39/1)
        - Trombone (Box-folder 39/2)
        - Drums (Box-folder 39/3)
        - Piano (Box-folder 39/4-40/1)
        - Violin A (Box-folder 40/2)
        - Violin B (Box-folder 40/3)
        - Violin B-D (Box-folder 40/4)
        - Violin C (Box-folder 41/1)
        - Violin D (Box-folder 41/2)
        - Viola (Box-folder 41/3-4)
        - Cello (Box-folder 41/5-42/1)
        - Bass (Box-folder 42/2-3)
        - Cold winter: discarded complete orchestrations (Box-folder 42/4)
        - Crackerbarrel bunk: discarded complete orchestrations (Box-folder 42/5)
        - Crackerbarrel encore: discarded complete orchestrations (Box-folder 42/6)
        - Goodbye, dear friend, goodbye: discarded complete orchestrations (Box-folder 42/7)
        - I do, he doesn't: discarded complete orchestrations (Box-folder 42/8)
        - Man never marries a wife: discarded complete orchestrations (Box-folder 43/1)
        - Proposal cue no. 1: proposal-masters (Box-folder 43/2)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Discarded full scores (Box-folder 43/3-4)
        - Miscellaneous scripts and lyrics (Box-folder 43/5)
        - Conductor parts (Box-folder 43/6)
        - Conductor's score (positive print) (Box-folder 43/7-8)
        - Master copies-early rehearsal versions (Box-folder 44/1-2)
        - Masters of conductor's score (Box-folder 44/3-4)
        - Original audition copies (a masters) (Box-folder 44/5)
        - Pencil origins-audition copies (Box-folder 45/1)
        - Pencil origins-rehearsal copies (Box-folder 45/2)
        - Positive of rehearsal copies (old and new) (Box-folder 45/3)
        - Routines to fix (Box-folder 45/4)
      - Scripts
        - Choose your partner (Box-folder 46/1-3)
        - Courtin' time (Box-folder 46/4-6)
        - Audition script (revised), Missing p. 4-5 (Box-folder 46/7)
        - Suggested revisions and running order (Box-folder 46/8)
    - Curtain going up, 1952, Various writers
      - Piano-vocal scores or lead sheets
        - Curtain going up opening, Music and lyrics by Michael Brown (Box-folder 47/1)
        - Dr. Scholl, Music and lyrics by Charlotte Kent (Box-folder 47/2)
        - Fall River folly, Music and lyrics by Michael Brown (Box-folder 47/3)
        - I gotta make my own music, Music by Arthur Siegel, lyrics by Charlotte Kent (Box-folder 47/4)
        - I love you, I love you, I love you, Music and lyrics by Michael Brown (Box-folder 47/5)
        - Indian giver, Music and lyrics by Irvin Graham (Box-folder 47/6-7)
        - Let me love you, Music and lyrics by Bart Howard (Box-folder 47/8)
        - Lot of lovin' (Bill's chorus), Music and lyrics by Charlotte Kent (Box-folder 47/9)
        - Miss Rhinestone, Music and lyrics by Irvin Graham (Box-folder 47/10)
        - Money, Music and lyrics by Ed Hein (Box-folder 47/11)
        - Opening-Act I (Box-folder 47/12)
        - Rich woman, Music and lyrics by Irvin Graham (Box-folder 47/13)
        - The swamp boy, Music and lyrics by Michael Brown (Box-folder 47/14)
        - Swamp boy/Buddy 'o dance, Short score (Box-folder 47/15)
        - Take care of yourself, Music and lyrics by Bart Howard (Box-folder 47/16)
        - This is the day, Music and lyrics by Bart Howard (Box-folder 47/17)
        - Unidentified music (Box-folder 47/18)
        - Vocal routines (Box-folder 47/19)
      - Notes (Box-folder 47/20)
    - Damn yankees, 1955, Music and lyrics by Richard Adler and Jerry Ross
      - Full score masters
        - Back home (Box-folder 112/1)
        - Bows (Box-folder 112/2)
        - Court room black out (Box-folder 112/3)
        - Devil music (Box-folder 112/4)
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 112/5)
        - Exit music (Box-folder 112/6)
        - Fanfare (Box-folder 112/7)
        - The game (Box-folder 112/8)
        - Goodbye, old girl (Box-folder 112/9)
        - Goodbye, old girl reprise (Box-folder 112/10)
        - Heart/Heart encore/Heart reprise (Box-folder 112/11)
        - A little brains, a little talent (Box-folder 112/12)
        - A man doesn't know (Box-folder 112/13)
        - A man doesn't know finale (Box-folder 112/14)
        - A man doesn't know reprise (Box-folder 112/15)
        - Near to you (Box-folder 112/16)
        - Not Meg (Box-folder 112/17)
        - Overture revised/overture intro (Box-folder 112/18)
        - Shoeless Joe from Hannibal, Mo. (Box-folder 112/19)
        - Shoeless Joe from Hannibal, Mo. dance (Box-folder 112/20)
        - Shoeless Joe from Hannibal, Mo. new finale (Box-folder 112/21)
        - Shoeless Joe from Hannibal, Mo. vocal (Box-folder 112/22)
        - Six months out of every year (Box-folder 112/23)
        - Those were the good old days (Box-folder 112/24)
        - Two lost souls (Box-folder 112/25)
        - Whatever Lola wants (Box-folder 112/26)
        - Whatever Lola wants ork (Box-folder 112/27)
        - Who's got the pain? (Box-folder 112/28)
    - Dance me a song, 1950, Music and lyrics by James Shelton and others
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Adam's rib (Box-folder 47/21)
        - My little dog has ego (Box-folder 47/22)
    - Delilah see The vamp
    - Early to bed, 1943, Music by Fats Waller, lyrics by George Marion, Jr.
      - Get away, young man, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 47/23)
    - The fabulous doll, 1946, Alternate title: The doll girl; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Clay Warnick
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Born with a feather in my throat (Box-folder 47/24)
        - Change of scene (Box-folder 47/25)
        - The evening angelus (Box-folder 47/26)
        - Exquisite sequence (Box-folder 47/27)
        - The fabulous doll (Box-folder 47/28)
        - Finaletto (Act I, scene 1) (Box-folder 47/29)
        - Finaletto (Act II, scene 1) (Box-folder 47/30)
        - Guggeinheimer trade-mark (Box-folder 47/31)
        - I love a shy young man (Box-folder 47/32)
        - If I'd only had a sister (Box-folder 47/33)
        - I'm a great big bulging brain (Box-folder 47/34)
        - I'm a great big bulging brain encore (Box-folder 47/35)
        - I'm a great big bulging brain finale tag (Box-folder 47/36)
        - I'm a panic with a pipe (Box-folder 47/37)
        - Only a doll (Box-folder 47/38)
        - Opening chorus of friars (Oh where oh where are the good old days) (Box-folder 47/39)
        - Pay-day (Box-folder 48/1)
        - Pay-day reprise (Box-folder 48/2)
        - There is always a happy ending (Box-folder 48/3)
        - Too lovely to last (Box-folder 48/4)
        - Twice as beautiful (Box-folder 48/5)
        - Wedding sequence (Box-folder 48/6)
        - Wedding wine (opening Act II) (Box-folder 48/7)
        - The world is a wonderful place (Box-folder 48/8)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified music (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Script materials
        - The dancing dolly or Three castles, Outline by Mervyn Nelson (Box-folder 48/10)
        - The fabulous doll, Script by Walter Catlett and George Poultney
          - Act I (Box-folder 48/11)
          - Act II (Box-folder 48/12)
        - The fabulous doll (2) (Box-folder 48/13-14)
        - The doll girl, Act II; 1935 May 10 (Box-folder 48/15)
    - A family affair, 1965, Music by John Kander, lyrics by James and William Goldman
      - Harmony, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 48/16)
    - Finian's rainbow, 1947, Music by Burton Lane, lyrics by E.Y. Harburg
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - How are things in Glocca Morra (Box-folder 48/17)
        - If this isn't love (Box-folder 48/18)
        - Look to the rainbow (Box-folder 48/19)
        - That old devil moon (Box-folder 48/20)
    - Forbidden melody, 1936, Music by Sigmund Romberg, lyrics by Otto Harbach
      - You are all I wanted, Full score, vocal arrangement/piano-vocal score (Box-folder 48/21)
    - Gentlemen prefer blondes, 1949, Music by Jule Styne, lyrics by Leo Robin
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Bye bye baby (Box-folder 49/1)
        - Diamonds are a girls best friend (Box-folder 49/2)
        - Gentlemen prefer blondes/Finale (Box-folder 49/3)
        - I'm just a little girl from Little Rock (Box-folder 49/4)
        - I'm keeping cool with Coolidge (Box-folder 49/5)
        - It's delightful down in Chile (Box-folder 49/6)
        - It's high time (Box-folder 49/7)
        - Just a kiss apart (Box-folder 49/8)
        - Mamie is Mimi (Box-folder 49/9)
        - Music for newspaper drop, Piano score; Notes on verso (Box-folder 49/10)
        - Sunshine (Box-folder 49/11)
        - You say you care (Box-folder 49/12)
        - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 49/13)
    - The gift of the magi, 1958, TV musical, music and lyrics by Richard Adler
      - Full scores
        - A better word than love (Box-folder 113/1)
        - Bridge to bank (Box-folder 113/2)
        - Christmas in your heart (Box-folder 113/3)
        - Company man (Box-folder 113/4)
        - Finale (Box-folder 113/5)
        - The flat (Box-folder 113/6)
        - Hair song (Box-folder 113/7)
        - My sugar (Box-folder 113/8)
        - The name's the same (Box-folder 113/9)
        - Never! (Box-folder 113/10)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 113/11)
        - Opening Act III (Box-folder 113/12)
        - Opening Act IV (Box-folder 113/13)
        - Opening credits (Box-folder 113/14)
        - Opening incidental (Box-folder 113/15)
        - Overture (Box-folder 113/16)
        - The pawnshop (Box-folder 113/17)
        - Sex creeps in (Box-folder 113/18)
        - Sheaffer opening and closing (Box-folder 113/19)
        - Suffragette (Box-folder 113/20)
        - Tag, Act III (Box-folder 113/21)
        - The watch (Box-folder 113/22)
        - What to do? (Box-folder 113/23)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentified music (Box-folder 113/24)
      - Piano-vocal scores/piano-conductor scores/short scores
        - A better word than love (Box-folder 49/14)
        - Christmas in your heart (Box-folder 49/15)
        - Company men (Box-folder 49/16)
        - Finale (Box-folder 49/17)
        - Hair song (Box-folder 49/18)
        - My sugar, Incomplete (Box-folder 49/19)
        - The names the same (Box-folder 49/20)
        - Never! (Box-folder 49/21)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 49/22)
        - Opening Act III (Box-folder 49/23)
        - Opening Act IV (Box-folder 49/24)
        - Opening credits (Box-folder 49/25)
        - Overture (Box-folder 49/26)
        - Sex creeps in (Box-folder 49/27)
        - Sheaffer opening and closing (Box-folder 49/28)
        - Sheaffer opening and closing, Parts (Box-folder 49/29)
        - Tag Act III (Box-folder 49/30)
        - What to do? (Box-folder 49/31)
    - The girl in pink tights, 1954, Music by Sigmund Romberg, adapted by Walker, lyrics by Leo Robin
      - Full scores
        - The amazons (Box-folder 113/25)
        - Bacchanale (Box-folder 113/26)
        - Back to class (Box-folder 113/27)
        - Back to school (new) (Box-folder 113/28)
        - The bats (Box-folder 113/29)
        - Bowling Green cross (Box-folder 113/30)
        - Bridge to street (Box-folder 113/31)
        - Cake-walk (Box-folder 113/32)
        - The cardinal's guard (Box-folder 113/33)
        - Clyde's lesson/Pas de deux reprise (Box-folder 113/34)
        - Crazy tag (Box-folder 113/35)
        - Curtain Act I (Box-folder 113/36)
        - Curtain Act II (Box-folder 113/37)
        - Dalliance (Box-folder 113/38)
        - Dancing is easy (Box-folder 113/39)
        - The duel (Box-folder 113/40)
        - Etude (Box-folder 114/1)
        - Exit march (Box-folder 114/2)
        - Explosion/Firemen/Finale Act I (Box-folder 114/3)
        - La femme fatale (Box-folder 114/4)
        - La femme fatale tag (Box-folder 114/5)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 114/6)
        - The flag (Box-folder 114/7)
        - Free to love (Box-folder 114/8)
        - Fun! (Box-folder 114/9)
        - Going to the devil (Box-folder 114/10)
        - Hallucination (Box-folder 114/11)
        - I promised their mothers (Box-folder 114/12)
        - I promised their mothers (mother's reprise) (Box-folder 114/13)
        - In Paris and in love (Box-folder 114/14)
        - Lesson (Box-folder 114/17)
        - Let's pretent (Box-folder 114/18)
        - Lost in loveliness (Box-folder 114/19)
        - Lost in loveliness short version (Box-folder 114/20)
        - Lost in loveliness utility (Box-folder 114/21)
        - Love is the funniest thing (Box-folder 114/22)
        - My heart won't say goodbye (Box-folder 114/23)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 115/1)
        - Opening scene I (Box-folder 115/2)
        - Overture (Box-folder 115/3)
        - The parade (Box-folder 115/4)
        - Pas de deux (Box-folder 115/5)
        - Poster transition (Box-folder 115/6)
        - Rehearsal conflict (Box-folder 115/7)
        - The restaurant (Box-folder 115/8)
        - The siren (Box-folder 115/9)
        - Solo variation (Box-folder 115/10)
        - Temporary entr’acte/Bridge from Lost in loveliness/When I am free to love (Box-folder 115/11)
        - That naughty show (Box-folder 115/12)
        - Up in the elevated railway (Box-folder 115/13)
        - Up in the elevated railway finale (Box-folder 115/14)
        - Up in the elevated railway utility (Box-folder 115/15)
        - We're all in the same boat (Box-folder 115/16)
        - We're all in the same boat utility (Box-folder 115/17)
        - When I am free to love utility (Box-folder 115/18)
        - You've got to be a little crazy (Box-folder 115/19)
        - Zizi's variation (Box-folder 115/20)
        - Miscellaneous score fragments (Box-folder 115/21)
      - Piano-vocal scores/piano-conductor scores/short scores
        - Bacchanale (Box-folder 49/32)
        - Ballet conflict (Box-folder 49/33)
        - The bats (Box-folder 49/34)
        - Bowling green cross (Box-folder 49/35)
        - Bridge to street (Box-folder 49/36)
        - Cake-walk (Box-folder 49/37)
        - Curtain Act II (Box-folder 49/38)
        - Dalliance (Box-folder 49/39)
        - Dancing is easy (Box-folder 49/40)
        - The duel (Box-folder 49/41)
        - Elevated finale (Box-folder 50/1)
        - Elevated railway (Box-folder 50/2)
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 50/3)
        - Exit march (Box-folder 50/4)
        - Explosion (Box-folder 50/5)
        - La femme fatale (Box-folder 50/6)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 50/7)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 50/8)
        - Firemen (Box-folder 50/9)
        - The flag (Box-folder 50/10)
        - Free to love (Box-folder 50/11)
        - Free to love reprise (Box-folder 50/12)
        - Free to love utility (Box-folder 50/13)
        - Going to the devil (Box-folder 50/14)
        - Hallucination (Box-folder 50/15)
        - I promised their mothers (Box-folder 50/16)
        - I promised their mothers reprise (Box-folder 50/17)
        - In Paris and in love (Box-folder 50/18)
        - In Paris and in love utility (Box-folder 50/19)
        - Intro to elevated railway (Box-folder 50/20)
        - Let's pretend (Box-folder 50/21)
        - Lost in loveliness (Box-folder 50/22)
        - Lost in loveliness reprise (Box-folder 50/23)
        - Lost in loveliness utility (Box-folder 50/24)
        - Love is the funniest thing (Box-folder 50/25)
        - Melodrama (Box-folder 51/1)
        - My heart won't say goodbye (Box-folder 51/2)
        - My heart won't say goodbye utility (Box-folder 51/3)
        - Niblo's change (Box-folder 51/4)
        - Opening Act I (Box-folder 51/5)
        - Overture (Box-folder 51/6)
        - The parade (Box-folder 51/7)
        - Pas de deux (Box-folder 51/8)
        - Rehearsal conflict (Box-folder 51/9)
        - Temporary overture (Box-folder 51/10)
        - That naughty show (Box-folder 51/11)
        - We're all in the same boat (Box-folder 51/12)
        - We're all in the same boat utility (Box-folder 51/13)
        - You've got to be a little bit crazy (Box-folder 51/14)
        - Zi-Zi's lesson (Box-folder 51/15)
        - Bound piano-conductor score, 2 volumes (Box 116)
      - Bound parts, Reed I; Reed III; Trumpet 1-2; Percussion; Violin A-C; Bass (Box 52)
      - Parts, unbound, some reverse transparencies
        - Reed 1 (Box-folder 53/1-2)
        - Reed 2 (Box-folder 53/3-5)
        - Reed 3 (Box-folder 53/6-8)
        - Reed 4 (Box-folder 54/1-3)
        - Horns 1-2 (Box-folder 54/4-55/1)
        - Horn 3 (Box-folder 55/2-4)
        - Trumpets 1-2 (Box-folder 55/5-7)
        - Trombone (Box-folder 56/1-3)
        - Drums (Box-folder 56/4-5)
        - Harp (Box-folder 56/7-57/2)
        - Violin A (Box-folder 57/3)
        - Violin A-C (Box-folder 57/4-5)
        - Violin B (Box-folder 57/6-58/1)
        - Violin D (Box-folder 58/2-4)
        - Viola (Box-folder 58/5-6)
        - Cello (Box-folder 59/1-2)
        - Bass (Box-folder 59/3-5)
        - Pas de deux (Box-folder 59/6)
        - Miscellaneous/unidentified parts (Box-folder 59/7)
      - Choral arrangement (Box-folder 59/8-9)
      - Scripts
        - Book by Jerome Chodorov and Joseph Fields, 1952 Aug. 18, Laid in: carbons of correspondence and other materials (Box-folder 59/10)
        - Script, corrected 1953 Nov. 13, 23, 25 (Box-folder 60/1)
        - Script with "Song ploy-analyzed for characters" (Box-folder 60/2)
        - 11 character part books (Box-folder 60/3)
        - 3 chorus books (Box 60)
    - Glad to see you, 1944, Music by Jule Styne, lyrics by Sammy Cahn